It's how you wear the mask that matters.
Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse is a animation,
action, adventure film directed by Kemp Powers.
After reuniting with Gwen Stacy, Brooklyn’s full-time, friendly neighborhood Spider-Man is catapulted across the Multiverse, where
he encounters the Spider Society, a team of Spider-People charged with protecting the Multiverse's very existence.
But when the heroes clash on how to handle a new threat, Miles finds himself pitted against
the other Spiders and must set out on his own to save those he loves most.
Miles Morales (voice), played by Shameik Moore.
Gwen Stacy (voice), played by Hailee Steinfeld.
Jeff Morales (voice), played by Brian Tyree Henry.
Rio Morales (voice), played by Luna Lauren Vélez.
Peter B. Parker (voice), played by Jake Johnson.
Miguel O'Hara (voice), played by Oscar Isaac.
Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse is an upcoming American animated superhero film
based on Marvel Comics featuring the character Miles Morales / Spider-Man.
Directed by Bob Persichetti and Justin K.
Thompson from a screenplay by the writing team of Phil Lord and Christopher Miller alongside David Callaham, it is the direct
sequel to Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse (2023) and the final installment in the Spider-Verse trilogy.
Shameik Moore stars as the voice of Miles, alongside Hailee Steinfeld, Jason
Schwartzman, Karan Soni, Daniel Kaluuya, and Nicolas Cage.
The film continues from the cliffhanger ending of Across the Spider-Verse, with
Miles trapped in an alternate universe trying to save his family.
It is produced by Columbia Pictures and Sony Pictures Animation,
and is to be distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing.
Sony began developing a sequel to Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse before that film's release in 2018,
and eventually decided to split it into two films, which was revealed in December 2021.
The third film was titled in April 2022 and given a March 2024 release date, while early work
coincided with the production of Across the Spider-Verse before that film was prioritized.
The script and animation of Beyond the Spider-Verse underwent significant changes before
the 2023 SAG-AFTRA strike delayed production and its release date in July.
After the second film's release and the end of the
strike, work resumed in December.
The writers and directors were revealed a year later, and a
new release date was announced in March 2025.
Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse is scheduled to be
released in the United States on June 18, 2027.
The film explores themes of new york city, hero,
sacrifice, secret identity, superhero.
The tone is thought_provoking.